

- ducbinhnguyen23@gmail.com
- +358417233391
- Vaasa, Finland

# **CORE SKILLS**

- <u>CONCEPTUALS</u>: Object Oriented Programming, SOLID Principles, REST, Git, Agile, UX Design.
- <u>LANGUAGES</u>: C#, Javascript,
   Typescript, Python, Java
- FRAMEWORKS & LIBRARIES: ASP
   .NET Core, NodeJS, LINQ, XUnit,
   React, Jest, .NET Core,
   ElectronJS, Android, React
   Native, Pytest, Vue3, NextJS,
   LangChain, OpenCV
- DATABASES & ORM: PostgreSQL, MS SQL Server, MongoDB, Entity
   Framework, Azure SQL
- <u>DEVOPS & CLOUD</u>: Github Action,
   Docker, Azure DevOps, Jira,
   Kubernetes, Azure Cloud

# **LANGUAGES**

- English: Fluent
- Vietnamese: Native
- Finnish: Elementary

# **ACCOMPLISHMENTS**

- Azure Developer Associate (AZ-204)
- Full Stack Open CI/CD&
- <u>Full Stack Open TypeScript@</u>
- Full Stack Open React Native&
- Full Stack Open GraphQL&
- Full Stack Open MERN Stack
- Al For Everyone
- Full Stack Integrify@

# BINH NGUYEN

## SOFTWARE DEVELOPER



As a Gen Z tech enthusiast with two years of hands-on experience in Software Development, my personal standards in programming are rigorous, focusing on both the internal and external aspects of every product.

I am fully committed to dedicating my heart and soul to each creation and always open to discuss in cloud development and AI Generative solutions.

# **WORK EXPERIENCES**

#### SOFTWARE DEVELOPER TRAINEE

Integrify | Helsinki, Finland (January 2024 - September 2024) | 9 mos

Technologies Combined: Microsoft Graph, Azure Functions, ASP.NET Core Identity, EntralD, Azure App Services, Azure Cosmos DB, Azure Service Bus, Azure Monitor, Azure Blob Storage, C#, .NET, REST API, TypeScript, React, Redux Toolkit, React Router, PostgreSQL, CI/CD Pipeline, LINQ, XUnit, Entity Framework.

- Designed and implemented advanced Front-End solutions for the Synchronize Ecommerce Platform, enhancing user experience.
- Led a team of 3 developers in developing robust Back End solutions successfully and integrated an Event Management API with Azure Cloud Services for system reliability and scalability.

#### THESIS RESEARCHER

ITD Group | VAMK | Vaasa, Finland (September 2023 - May 2024) | 9 mos

Technologies Combined: Python, Pytest, Flask API, YOLO, OpenCV.

- Conducted AI script tests for Video Management System.
- Created test reports and onboarding docs, set up a simulation environment for testing and validation.

#### STUDENT PARTNER

Pinja Oy | Vaasa, Finland (September 2023 - December 2023) | 4 mos

**Technologies Combined**: Javascript, Vue3.js, Bryntum library, Azure DevOps.

- Designed, developed, and built the Pinja Gantt Chart frontend project, working with Vue3.js under the guidance of Pinja company in the collaboration with 2 other developers.
- Deliver successfully the front-end Gantt Chart to the project manager.



#### SOFTWARE ENGINEER INTERN

ITD Group | Ho Chi Minh city, Vietnam (January 2023 - August 2023) | 8 mos

**Technologies Combined:** C#, Winform, DevExpress, Angular, React, ElectronJS, Python, Pytest, Numpy, MS SQL Server, YOLO, OpenCV, Flask API.

- Worked with cross-functional teams of fifteen members.
- Gathered feedback for application enhancements, successfully delivering 3 updated versions of the voting counter application.
- Served as an AI API Testing Engineer in a microservice team of 4 software engineers, contributing to test reports and API documentation.
- Trained 1 trainee to test the Video Management System with Pytest and OpenCV.

#### **CO-FOUNDER - CREATIVE MANAGER**

Synchronize Recording Studio | Vaasa, Finland (April 2020 - April 2022) | 2 yrs

Technologies Combined: Adobe Photoshop, Ableton Live, FL Studio

- Collaboration with over thirty industry partners.
- Successfully released twenty eight music products to the market
- Successfully protected over twenty music copyrights.
- Web design, pattern design, brand and label design.
- Worked with advertising platform of Google and meta to reach the targeted audiences.
- Official Youtube channel: https://www.youtube.com/@synchronizerecordingstudio6693

# **EDUCATION**

#### **BACHELOR OF INFORMATION TECHNOLOGY**

Vaasa University of Applied Sciences (VAMK) | Vaasa, Finland | Graduated in May 2024

### **FULLSTACK DEVELOPMENT PROGRAM**

Integrify Academy | Helsinki, Finland | Graduated in June 2024